A Guide to the Papers of Nancy Byrd Turner, 1831-1987
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- MANUSCRIPTS & MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS
  - Phonodisk Records
    - Nancy Byrd Turner reading her own poems, side 9, 1955 Jul 27, 10 inch disk
      Includes: "Sic Transit," "A Statue of Washington in the North," "Clovelly Clings Above the Sea."
    - "Songs from New Music Horizons," Columbia Records, 1950, 10 inch disk
    - "Songs from New Music Horizons," Columbia Records, 1950, 10 inch disk
    - "The Creation," Wedgemere Studios, Winchester, [Massachusetts], n.d., 10 inch disk